[{
    "theme": "Objetos desaparecidos en el tiempo",
    "langread": "es",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "sense",
            "answers": ["sentido"]
        },
        {
            "question": "small",
            "answers": ["pequeños"]
        },
        {
            "question": "cute / pretty",
            "answers": ["lindo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "photo album",
            "answers": ["álbum de foto"]
        },
        {
            "question": "sometimes",
            "answers": ["a veces"]
        },
        {
            "question": "the same",
            "answers": ["lo mismo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to touch",
            "answers": ["tocar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "memory / souvenir",
            "answers": ["recuerdo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "nostalgic",
            "answers": ["nostálgica"]
        },
        {
            "question": "a problem",
            "answers": ["un problema"]
        },
        {
            "question": "map",
            "answers": ["mapa"]
        },
        {
            "question": "telephone / phone",
            "answers": ["teléfono"]
        },
        {
            "question": "bicycle",
            "answers": ["bicicleta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to postpone",
            "answers": ["posponer"]
        }
    ]
}]
